America's most notorious female serial killer.
Aileen Wuornos: American Boogeywoman is a horror,
thriller film directed by Daniel Farrands.
Based on Aileen Wuornos’s early life, this is the true story of  America’s most notorious
female serial killer, who went on a killing spree in Florida in 1989 and 1990.
What few people know, is that back in 1976 a young and beautiful Aileen Wuornos arrived in Florida searching for a new life that would help her
escape her tragic past, married a wealthy Yacht Club President and had the chance to start again as part of Florida’s high society...
or did she?
Aileen Wuornos, played by Peyton List.
Lewis Fell, played by Tobin Bell.
Jennifer Fell, played by Lydia Hearst.
Victor Miller, played by Nick Vallelonga.
Grady Miller, played by Swen Temmel.
Mitch Miller, played by Andrew Biernat.
Aileen Wuornos: American Boogeywoman is a 2021 American horror
thriller film written and directed by Daniel Farrands.
It shows a fictionalized version of the early life of serial killer
Aileen Wuornos, with some real facts from her biography.
It stars Peyton List as Wuornos, supporting cast includes Tobin Bell, Lydia
Hearst, Nick Vallelonga, Swen Temmel, and Andrew Biernat.
The film was released as video-on-demand on October 8,
2021, and on DVD on October 15, 2021.
The film explores themes of florida, based on true
story, murder, serial killer, murderer.
The tone is dark and intense.